Hello, everyone. Welcome back to to this another new tutorial topic. So to the here, I'll create the MySQL for the primary key
constant in the MySQL of the management studio. Okay. So first of all, here, I can design for the efficient and the
whole structured database. Okay. So just simply explain for the MySQL, the primary key constant is used to uniquely
identify the report in a table and ensure that two can have the same primary key value. Okay. So now, just explore how it
works with the example. So first of all, I can already create for the table structure for student and here it's simply
create for the three columns. So first of all, the students are the primary key and the second one is in the students name and the
email format. Okay. So now here, the primary key for the first year, the students ID, this column is the primary key for the
students table. Okay. And now here, I can identify in this table and suppose I can try successfully cleared. So first of all, here, I can select and
here, I can just select and execute now. And you can see here, this command is completely successfully created and here I created for
the separation is successfully and MySQL is well created completely. And the next system here, I can another example, I can add the
primary key constantly. So now just here, I can create the students table and the next system here, I can use for another
table, just select. So first of all, just go here and select for the database and just go for the cells and also for
the table. And here is for the few tables, first is the employees, then the products and for the students table. Okay.
So now here, execute. So first of all, type and go to another file or segment and here, I can just go and alter for
here the table. Okay. And select from here, the employee's table. Okay. And then the next step, I can add for the primary key. Okay. So define for here,
the primary key constant. And in this inside, I can just try for here the underscore ID. Okay. So now I can just simply
find and here, first of all, I can select all and execute now and just create here, not too so here, I can choose the cells and then now just
I can again, here, I can just again, select and execute. And you can see here, already primary key is defined. Okay. So here already defined. So you can see just go here, the column inside. And you can see here already defined.
part, which is called the ID, the primary key. Okay. So here, this is not defined really now. And now just go for here, the next step. Okay. So first of all, I can insert this data into the table with the primary key. Okay. So first of all, I can remove this. Okay.
So remove this statement and just here, I can type this insert into. Okay. So here, I can create for the insert into select for
students table and in this inside, just go for here, Jake. So first of all, here, I can create the primary key, suppose like the students
underscore ID, it is called the primary key. And also here, I can feel this student underscore the main column and also here, define this email column. Okay.
So this is perfect. And then go for the next given here, I can sit for the some value. So first of all, I can define for the
primary ID for six and there I can use for the name. Zara. Okay. And also here, I can create for
students email. So suppose you're I can use the Zara and
generate for example dot com. Okay. So now here, completely defined. And here, you see inserting the new students email for the student table.
And here, specifying for the student side is primary key and
use this attribute on here. And now I can just select. Okay.
So here, mistakenly modified the single quotation, it must be used. This quotation, okay. So now, just turn perfect and here.
I can select to learn now, just execute and you can see the on note completely affected. Okay.
So now just go again here and open another new one. And first of all, I'll just type this
select for star from the student stable and then execute for select for perfectly just execute. Now, you can see here
use for the students ID, the primary key and the students name and also for the email. Okay. So here, it is completely
created and this next step here, I can use for the update statement now. So just go for here. And first of all, I'll use for
just I can try. So first of all, I can just type update
students and next step here, I can use for the said, the students name,
students underscore the name column is equal to. So here, I can use for the name is
Jenny. So also here, I'll create for the word. So use the word statement, the
students underscore ID is equal to one. Okay. So now just try. So now just I can select and then
execute and you can see here, it is affected now. And the next step, I can just go for here,
then just begin for execute. Just second type select star from the student stable
and then select all and execute. As you can see here, so now just need to click find this
and now just select all and now just execute. And you can see here, this is the student side
just here. And now is completely used this and here, I can just use perfectly the primary key
constant in my skill and here, some practical example and I hope you find to the student helpful
stating for more my skill, tips and tricks. So thank you for watching. Okay.